{
    "id": "2bcb04ea207b4f7ba37cae9c8ce9ca66",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The parcels have ………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sent",
                "been sent",
                "been sending"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5ee56a24266a487d976c009d3324f931"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………….. the report.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is preparing",
                "is being prepared",
                "is prepared"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3618583567ba4d7caac60849b3ce42a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The seeds have not …………………. yet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been germinating",
                "germinated",
                "germinating"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24d6d8afa5f14c00b0241d1733cbd0a6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meal ………………… at 12 pm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "served",
                "was serving",
                "was served"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2154a07f54c54ba49a8ab3448a5d1254"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hostess ………………… everyone with open arms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "receiving",
                "received",
                "was received",
                "has receiving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fbe1a3cdfc6d4f2eabaa6ae45ff34e1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ...................... since Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has missing",
                "has missed",
                "has been missing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "10c03ba8f9774793bfdc1ff4e9448934"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ……………….. a ruckus.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "created",
                "was created",
                "was being created"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e51a0f5fc17642c3bbaab10221bfb6ff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys have ………………… in their assignments.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "been handing",
                "been handed",
                "handed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "28fa6434ffd345eb83ec6cf1cc9ea5b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother ………………… her son against working too hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "advised",
                "advising",
                "has been advised"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ab98fe2b4922420699ce6f1aabbbb4cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………. to quit smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "told",
                "was told",
                "has told"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6abd8df23e8b48af86bb58841c733261"
        }
    ]
}